[theme music playing]
[Camia] Nimfa got hold of my phone.
[Lily] Mom, we've known her for a while,
but we can't just trust her.
We can't take our chances.
Ivy's getting married to Arnaldo.
We can't let that happen.
Ivy and Arnaldo are now engaged.
Ivy had better watch out.
She'll regret saying yes to my son.
[Nimfa] Don't you ever think
that there's someone else
who's better for you?
A girl who can really love you?
Nimfa, wait. Can we not ruin what we have?
[Emilia] Congratulations
on your engagement, Ivy.
How thoughtful of you, Emilia.
But where's the bride's head?
[clamor]
I'm gonna do everything to ruin
your engagement with my son!
Bring it on!
[Ivy] I guess Emilia
and I will never get along,
so let's just call off the wedding.
[Arnaldo] Don't ever think about that.
I really think
Mom is just feeling insecure.
Our family is rich, but she isn't.
She doesn't know where
Grandpa's keeping our money.
Over my dead body, Arnaldo!
I will not apologize to her!
That woman will soon be my wife
and the future mother of my children.
Apologize to her,
or you're going to lose a son,
and gain one more enemy on your list.
[Ivy] I'm just wondering…
The Ardientes haven't kept their money
in any bank here or overseas.
[Diego] Why are you thinking that?
You're in the home of murderers.
You have to be careful.
[Ivy] If you don't stop
breathing down my neck, Emilia,
I'll take what little you still have left.
It won't just stress you out,
you might go into depression too.
[huffs]
Excuse me?
[sighs] Too bad there's no more cake left.
Okay.
Hm.
Good night, my future mother-in-law.
[mockingly]
You'll learn to love me someday.
[door slams]
[tense music playing]
[exhales sharply]
[plaintive music playing]
[Ivy] What are you doing?
It's dangerous here.
[Diego] What you're doing
is far more dangerous.
Arnaldo said the Ardientes
have not stashed off their money
in any bank.
So I figured it might be here
in the mansion.
Diego, if we find their money,
we can take down the Ardientes for good.
[Emilia] I knew it.
[taunting] Hey, Ivy.
I will find you, and I will catch you.
Ivy will only put herself in more danger
the longer she stays in that house.
[suspenseful music playing]
[door creaks]
[suspenseful music swells]
[suspenseful music continues playing]
[vehicle engine rumbles]
[phone rings]
Mom?
[sighs] I got to talk to you finally.
I've been worried since last night.
I was just about to go to your house.
-Let's meet up somewhere.
-All right. I'll be there.
-I'll see you, Mom.
-Okay.
[ominous music playing]
-Oh, hey. Good morning.
-Hi! Good morning.
I got here just in time.
Let me drive you home.
Um, I already had my driver
pick me up. But thank you.
-Just see me out.
-Okay, I will.
-Take care today, okay?
-You too.
-I'll miss you.
-I'll miss you more.
[phone rings]
Hello?
Camia's meeting with someone.
I bet it's someone important.
She was in a hurry.
It might be the person helping her?
It might be Ivy Aguas.
She was here at the mansion,
and she left in a hurry too.
Anyway,
this is what you'll do.
You follow Camia,
while I follow Ivy Aguas.
Okay, bye.
[suspenseful music playing]
[suspenseful music continues playing]
[suspenseful music swells]
[suspenseful music intensifies]
[elevator bell pings]
-Stay here. Don't follow me.
-Yes, ma'am.
[suspenseful music continues playing]
This time, Auntie Claire,
we'll see for ourselves
just what Ivy Aguas' ties
to Camia Cruz really are.
Let's go. Let the hunt begin.
[suspenseful music playing]
[suspenseful music continues playing]
[suspenseful music swells]
-Oh, hi!
-Hi, you're here.
Remember me? I'm Ivy Aguas.
-Yes.
-Hello.
-Hi. Nice to meet you.
-You too.
Yes, ma'am?
Um… Miss, have you seen
a lady with two bodyguards?
No, ma'am. Try checking
with the next store.
So, um…
-Is everything set?
-Yes, ma'am.
Sorry, I hope I'm not disturbing anything.
Actually, I'm waiting for someone.
[waitress] Have you placed
your order, ma'am?
Anything else, ma'am? All right.
If you need anything else, just say so.
Okay.
-She'll be here soon, I hope.
-[woman] Okay.
[tense music playing]
-Are we waiting for anyone else?
-Who are you expecting, ma'am?
Anyway, I have to go.
-Again, nice meeting you.
-Thank you.
-Nice to see you, bye.
[suspenseful music playing]
-Did you see anyone follow you?
-No, Lily.
Mom…
[upbeat music playing]
-Hey!
-Watch where you're going.
-[motorcycle engine rumbles]
Arnaldo is the key to finding out
where they're hiding the money.
But if I'm going to follow him,
I can't use this car.
-[jeep door slams]
-[jeep engine rumbles]
He's here, Mayor.
Yes, Grandpa? You called for me?
Yes, Arnaldo.
I want you to store this money
in our vault.
[bills rustling]
It's from Jaguar.
It seems like this small fry
wants to impress me.
[scoffs] Who knew Jaguar
was a generous man?
All right. I'll do it, Grandpa.
Remember, Arnaldo,
that money is very important
because we will use it for the elections.
Don't worry, I'll guard it
with all my life.
Santos, take this.
-We're going now, Grandpa.
-Okay.
I'm really sorry, Mom.
I'm sorry if we can only see
each other this way.
That we have to keep it a secret.
But we have to do this, Mom.
Because Emilia has been
keeping an eye on me.
I don't want her to ruin my plans.
I understand, Lily. But
I'm really worried about you.
What you're doing is very dangerous.
[suspenseful music playing]
[motorcycle engine rumbling]
[suspenseful music swells]
[suspenseful music continues playing]
I'm sorry, Mom.
But I've still got everything
under control.
So you don't have to worry.
You can't blame me for worrying, Lily.
Especially since you've reached the point
of faking a relationship with the enemy.
[plaintive music playing]
Mom, my relationship
with Arnaldo is all for show.
Everything is a lie.
It's all just part of my plan.
Maybe for you, but not for him.
Men like him are dangerous
when they get obsessed.
I've experienced it firsthand
with his father, Raul.
I know that, Mom.
But entering a relationship with Arnaldo
is the easiest way
to infiltrate the Ardientes.
Emilia's growing more suspicious
of me by the day,
and I know the congressman
hasn't trusted me since day one.
But Arnaldo? I've got him
wrapped around my finger.
He's fallen hard for me, Mom.
I've got him right where I want him.
How far will this go, Lily?
Until you end up marrying him?
Of course not.
I won't let it get that far.
Diego's helping me, Mom.
If his plan succeeds,
I have no doubt we can finally
take down the Ardientes.
[dramatic music playing]
[camera shutter clicking]
Looks like this is where
they're hiding the money.
[motorcycle engine revs]
I know you're worried, Mom.
And I'm sorry for making you
go through this every day.
I'm always praying for you.
And don't forget that
I'm always here for you.
Especially now that Emilia's
fighting you head-on.
You have to watch out for her.
I'm worried that Emilia
might get desperate
and force you to do the unthinkable.
She can try, Mom. But I won't let her.
We used to be helpless
against the Ardientes,
but now we can hold our own against them.
I was just a weak little girl
back then, Mom.
But now, I will use everything
Miss Prianka taught me…
against the Ardientes.
Lily, promise me that you won't get hurt.
Because I can never bear
the mere thought of you getting hurt.
You're the only one I have left.
I promise, Mom…
I promise you that
nothing will tear us apart.
Nothing will separate us again.
I promise, Mom.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Emilia] I have no patience for
Ivy, Aunt Claire.
I have to resort back to my old tricks.
Old tricks?
Like what you did to Camia Cruz?
[scoffs] Yes. Exactly, Auntie.
[henchman] Ma'am.
[suspenseful music playing]
Welcome, boys!
Are you ready for your new assignment?
-Yes, ma'am.
-Good.
[Raul] Papa.
I let myself in, sorry.
Uh…
Relax, Papa. I'm not going to do anything.
I… I just came here to talk to you.
You know what, Raul?
If there's one thing that I'll never do…
that is to let my guard down
when you're around.
What do you think of me? Stupid?
[scoffs]
Do you know what you remind me of?
A mad dog.
The type that just sits in one corner,
pretending to be calm,
-[snickers] mouth drooling…
-[scoffs]
but waiting to strike at any moment.
That's the way I see you.
Fine. You can say anything
you want to say about me.
You can say I'm like a mad dog.
-I can be, sometimes.
-[Julio scoffs]
If only to prove how much
I love your daughter, Emilia.
And that's the only reason I came here.
With all due respect,
I'm asking for your permission.
If it's all right with you,
I'd like to marry your daughter
for a second time.
[scoffs]
[cackles]
Oh!
[wheezing laughter]
Raul… [laughs uncontrollably]
I'll give it to you.
That was the funniest joke
I've ever heard in…
in forever!
Why don't you work as a carnival
clown or a court jester?
Who knows? Making people
laugh might be your calling.
[hoots and laughs]
I have no plans of making
other people happy.
I only want to make
your daughter, Emilia, happy.
[wheezing laughter]
[wheezes and coughs]
-Papa… Papa, are you okay?
-[wheezing laughter]
-Don't laugh too much, okay?
-[exaggerated heaving]
It's not good for you. You could
die from a heart attack!
-[wheezing laughter]
-Look…
Come to think of it, if you die,
you'd at least die happy,
because you died laughing.
[coughing] What did you say?
See? You've gone deaf too.
-Go on, Raul. Mock me!
-I'm not doing that.
-Mock me as much as you want.
-No. I won't do that.
But this I can assure you.
My daughter already made the mistake
of marrying a loser like you once.
And I don't think my daughter
will make that mistake
twice in her lifetime.
Come to think of it, if I was
given the chance to choose,
I'd rather let my daughter marry that…
that bastard, Jaguar! [laughing]
At least Jaguar has money.
Okay, that's all.
[door closes]
Could it be true that
Raul's turning over a new leaf?
Nah! Can't be.
[line ringing]
Hello.
Proceed with the plan.
[mahjong tiles rustling]
[suspenseful music playing]
Who are you?!
-[gunshot]
-Get down!
-Hands in the air!
-No! No! Don't!
We are Jaguar's men!
From now on, we'll be taking over
all of Julio Ardiente's gambling
operations. Is that clear?!
Gather all the money.
Let's go.
Um… Ma'am Governor, I'm really sorry.
Everything happened so fast.
She was gone before I knew it.
Well, Nimfa, just make sure
that she doesn't know
she's being followed, okay?
Of course, she doesn't.
She can't possibly know.
You better make sure, because you know
what will happen to you
if Camia finds out…
that you're following her.
Don't you dare push me.
Well, you're a feisty one, aren't you?
I just know how to play
my cards, just like you.
Then get your act together, dear.
And do your job properly.
If you want to keep your head.
You know what I can do.
I'm sure this funeral parlor
is just a front.
-Ivy, I'm going to break in.
-Diego, don't.
We have to make sure…
what's inside first.
We might find some important evidence.
That will pin down the Ardientes.
Exactly.
And Diego, I just thought…
you should focus on the campaign.
All right, Ivy.
The filing date is coming up soon.
Aunt Camia and I will come up with a plan.
I also want to thank you for everything.
Anything for you.
You stayed up all night
investigating. Again, thank you.
[Arnaldo] Ivy, who's that?
Who were you talking to?
[tense music swells]
[sighs] A representative from
Aguas Realty.
It's about some business in Manila.
They ran into some problems
because I wasn't there.
Hi.
What's with that look?
Are you getting jealous again?
Arnaldo, we already talked about
how I don't want
a partner who's the jealous type.
What are you implying? Not you too!
Your mom is already suspicious of me,
and now you're doubting me too?
Arnaldo, please! Can you please trust me?
How can I trust you?
I was just asking who you were talking to.
I have no idea why you and Mom
are always fighting,
or why she's always suspicious of you.
I was just asking
who you were talking to, okay?
I'm sorry if I upset you!
Why wouldn't I be upset?!
I know that you're doubting me even though
I was simply talking
to someone from Aguas Realty.
I'm having a problem with my business.
-Okay. Fine, fine, fine.
-Please. I don't like this!
Fine, fine. Fine!
How can I not react? You look
at me like you're doubting me.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry if I upset you.
It… it was just a question.
Okay, I-- I think the only way
we can fix this…
is for you to have dinner with my mom.
Okay? So we can fix this
problem once and for all.
[sighs]
Hon…
Of course. I'll do it for you.
Yes. I'll have dinner with your mom.
But the question is, is she ready too?
Yeah.
Yeah, she's ready. It's okay.
She said she has an appointment tomorrow,
so that should be fine.
That's… that's great.
See? Problem solved, then.
[giggles]
Hon…
I don't want us to fight.
Don't be jealous, okay?
You know you're the only one
I love, right?
I love you.
Do you love me?
Yeah. I love you.
-Yeah.
-You love me?
I do. I do.
[coos] Thanks, hon.
Mom.
-Ah, yes?
-Good news.
Ivy agreed to have dinner with you.
Wow. That's really great, son.
Don't worry. After the dinner,
this will all be over.
-I hope so.
-Yeah.
-All right. I'll be going now.
-All right.
[Rufo] Listen up.
Jaguar has a message for us. Watch.
[distorted voice]
Welcome. Welcome to my group.
I'm glad that we're one family now.
As your leader, I will be
generous, unlike Julio.
I want to assure you
that we're all equals here.
Everyone has a fair chance
of becoming king.
Money, women, everything,
I will give everything to each
and every one of you.
But I have just one thing
to ask in return.
You must not walk out
or betray the organization.
That way, everyone will be happy, right?
You're going down, Jaguar!
The congressman will bring you down!
Don't! I'll deal with him.
Stop right there! I won't hurt you.
[grunting]
When Congressman learns about
this, there will be hell to pay!
[grunts and groans]
The next time you try
to escape, I'll finish you off.
Mayor, Congressman, we'll have
a live band and street party,
so we can attract the young voters too.
We will also be holding
a fireworks display
as you announce your candidacy.
And how much is this package
gonna cost us?
Around 10 million for
the event alone, Congressman.
Ten million?
Pretty fair price.
Anyway, I've heard enough. You can go.
Thank you very much, Mr. Congressman.
-Thank you for coming.
-Thank you, Mayor.
[sighs]
Arnaldo, I'm sure Ivy
can sponsor this event for you.
Uh, Grandpa, if it's all right,
let's leave Ivy out of this.
Hmm?
I don't want her to think
that we're only after her money,
or that we're just using her.
But it's the truth, right?
You're only after her money.
Actually, no. Not anymore.
I… I care for her.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hold your horses, young man.
You can't fall in love with that woman.
I can. I'm already in love with her.
It's just that I can still
be smart at the same time.
Okay. It's your choice.
But I'm telling you, if this goes south…
I'm pulling the plug.
Not just on your dreams…
but also on the life of that
woman you're pining over.
Okay. Challenge accepted.
Okay. Here we go.
I'm sure that the upcoming
election will be a dirty one.
And I know that the Ardientes
won't accept defeat.
That's why we have to be ready
for anything.
We're ready to take them on.
I have faith that Diego will win.
They will not take away Diego's victory.
Okay, good. Let's win this.
We need to prepare a huge event
in time for the filing of your candidacy.
Something that will shock the Ardientes.
[Camia] I have an idea.
When Diego files for candidacy,
his supporters should be there.
Let's see if it doesn't stress
the Ardientes out.
[Marlon] That's good, Miss Camia.
She's right, Diego.
As early as now, we should gain
the support of important people.
We'll need their influence.
I'll take care of that.
I'll make sure that
our first mobilization effort
will be full of people.
-Hi, Papa, Arnaldo.
-Hi, Emilia.
Good that you two are here.
I heard the news, Papa.
I heard that Camia Cruz
is mobilizing people
for Diego's filing of candidacy.
And we have to stop that.
Arnaldo will be on top of that.
[sighs] You know, Emilia, you surprise me.
Where do you get all that information?
Well, Papa, I'm resourceful like you.
Good job. Keep it up.
Um, Papa, Arnaldo,
I'll leave you two here, okay?
I'll just prepare for my dinner with Ivy.
-Okay.
-Oh, by the way.
Please do keep that woman distracted.
I want Arnaldo to focus
on the upcoming elections.
-Yes, Papa. By all means.
-Okay.
Excuse me.
-Enjoy.
-Thank you.
-Arnaldo.
-Hmm?
Come with me to my meeting with
our people in the gambling den.
They're one of the keys
to securing your success
in the upcoming election.
-Sure. I'll be there.
-Okay.
You're good, kid. I'm impressed.
And in return, I'll give you
and your boss a bonus.
You don't get to say
when I'm getting a bonus.
You might be forgetting
that my boss is your partner.
My boss will take what's rightfully ours,
with or without your blessing.
You probably know that
it's not money my boss is after.
So, what's your boss after?
Tell me, and I'll give you that.
[phone rings]
Boss.
Okay.
My boss wants to talk to you.
Hello.
Yes.
Yes, I heard that
it's not money you want from me.
What do you need? Just tell me.
I can give you that.
[scoffs]
We're on the same side.
Who would have thought?
You want Julio Ardiente's head?
You know, I can give you what you want.
But I'm sorry to say that you're too late.
Because Julio Ardiente's head is mine.
I will kill him myself.
Tell your boss that we need to meet.
We need to talk.
Boss.
Yes.
Okay.
I'll tell Raul that you want
to meet him right away.
You're going to see that man
because you trust him?
No.
Because I don't trust anyone
in this world.
I only need him
to set my plans into motion.
Are you using me too?
Come here.
Natalie, you're different.
You're nothing like those other women.
If it weren't for you,
I wouldn't have turned things around.
That's really sweet of you to say.
So…
what are you planning now?
We'll celebrate.
We need to invite every
acquaintance of the Ardientes.
And everyone who worked for them.
We have to gain their trust.
We also need to invest
in the upcoming elections.
And who are we supporting?
My son, Diego, of course.
Because if he wins as governor,
Julio Ardiente will be ousted,
and they'll lose their grip on power.
Their days are numbered.
I will take Emilia's head.
And you…
I'll take Julio's last breath.
[tense music playing]
[phone rings]
-Emilia?
-Hello, Ivy.
-Are you excited for our dinner?
-Of course.
I am too. I shall see you.
-See you.
-Bye.
So very excited, Emilia.
[suspenseful music playing]
[phone rings]
-Diego.
-Hello, Ivy.
-How are you?
-I'm fine. Uh…
Emilia and I are having dinner
at the Viento.
Ivy…
Be careful.
Thank you, Diego. Don't worry,
I can handle myself.
-Thanks again.
-All right.
[suspenseful music playing]
[vehicle door opens]
[snaps fingers]
[vehicle door closes]
Go. Fly high, my vulture.
Just make sure that Ivy will be
reduced to a pulp of
rotting flesh the next time I see her.
As you wish, ma'am. We'll take care of it.
Fly high.
Go on, park the car.
You don't have to come with me.
[Emilia humming]
Like a moth in a spider's web.
Goodbye, Ivy Aguas.
[humming]
Cheers. [laughs]
Who are you? Where's Emilia?
[suspenseful music playing]
-Where is Emilia?
-[goon laughs]
[goons laughing]
I said, where is Emilia?
[goon laughs]
[grunts]
You!
[growls]
[grunts]
[action music playing]
-[groans]
-[grunts]
[grunts]
-[groans]
-[growls]
[growls]
[groans]
[grunts]
It's either something bad happened to her,
or worse, you're behind all this.
I won't let the Ardientes get away with
the things they do.
So I have to endure everything
no matter what.
I won't file for that damn candidacy
until I find Ivy.
That woman's trying to brainwash you.
I'm on the verge of forgetting
that you're my mother
and slapping your beautiful face!
If something happens to Ivy,
you will answer to me!
Remember that!
You bitch! Stop playing dumb
because I know
you hired those men to rape me!
[theme music fading]